saveyourlinks.com 2016-06-24

# Save Your Links - free, easy to use bookmark and favorites manager

Privacy Policy

* * *

The policy of Wizdata Systems, Inc. is to respect and protect the privacy of our users. This Privacy Policy discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices. We believe that electronic privacy is crucial for the ongoing success of the Internet as a service, commercial and entertainment medium. 

While we strive to deliver content and advertising that are specifically relevant to you, Wizdata Systems, Inc. does not sell, exchange, or release any of your individual personal information to a third party without you express permission. From time to time, we may introduce new products and services to our customers. To the extent these new products and services affect this policy, this policy will be modified or updated.

As part of the registration process, Wizdata Systems, Inc. users are asked to fill out a questionnaire. The information provided will not be released to any third party without the user’s express permission. The demographic information collected during the registration process will be used to refine and improve the site content, to determine informational advertisements, to provide specialized services and to measure site activity. We may count, track and aggregate the visitor’s activity into our analysis of general traffic flows at our site. To these ends, we may merge information about you, which may then be shared on an aggregated basis with our advertisers and business partners. However, we will not disclose your individual identity.

Use of cookies

Once the user completes the questionnaire form on the site, a "cookie" is placed on his or her computer. The purpose of the "cookie" is to allow access to Wizdata Systems, Inc. without the need to input a user name and password every time they access the site from the same computer. The cookie itself does not contain any personally identifying information. 

Other companies, which place advertising on our site, also have the ability to assign their cookies to you in a process not under our control. We are not responsible for their privacy policies or how they treat information about their users. However, Wizdata Systems, Inc. will not provide them with information without your consent.

Other circumstances

From time to time, Wizdata Systems, Inc. may sponsor promotional events, which require the collection, processing and storing of individual contact and demographic information to be used for the event. Wizdata Systems, Inc. may also co-sponsor these activities with other companies, in which case the user’s individual contact and demographic information is likely to be shared with the other participating sponsors. A registrant’s personal contact and demographic information will not be released to third parties or non-participating organizations without the user’s consent and Wizdata Systems, Inc. will request that co-sponsors of such events uphold the privacy of the registrants’ information.

When appropriate, an option will be made available for users during the event registration process to choose to receive information from third-party organizations.

You should be aware that when you voluntarily disclose personal information on the chat or discussion areas that information can be collected and used by other and may result in unsolicited messages from other parties.

This site is maintained by:

> Wizdata Systems, Inc.  
>  2001 Route 46, Suite 310  
>  Parsippany, NJ 07054  
> 

If you have any questions about this privacy statement or the practices of this site, please contact us at [support@saveyourlinks.com](mailto:support@saveyourlinks.com)
